year and more we ask you to make it that way. We ask that you will give them this and we
can help them when they're in the weary area. It's exhausting, helping them be strong and continue
to guide them. Jesus, thank you for that.
Thank you.
Thanks for that.
Congratulations to the five of the United States of America and to the Rio de Janeiro for which
the United States of America, the United States of America, the United States of America,
the United States of America, the United States of America, the United States of America.
I'm a force public input on scale to approach what the U.S. is known as the U.S. is to address
the authority on any of the agenda.
There will be none of the five of us can send agenda staff is recommending the United States in
seven which all claims and minutes for the consent agenda. No questions on any of those items
asked us to bring the support and have a note in a minute.
This is the next project that we are going to tackle in house with our born unit.
I will be doing these three water lines.
And this is all political water.
Yes sir.
You have a lot of drinking water, yes sir.
Any questions for Tyler on this project?
Okay.
Thanks, Tyler.
Adam 9 is new business and a new business.
Ten is staff report to join the project available.
A lot of them is trustee community announcements and announcements.
There we are.
And for all of us adjournment, we have a motion to adjourn the S.J.
Motion to adjourn.